Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world's a mix of colors and blue
Truth and falsehood blur our eyes
Use your heart to truly see
Find the truth is not far away
Hey you could do better
True and false
Can't escape this mental haze
Take along all your courage
Maybe then you'll save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Runaway Princess
Lorena
Princess, please accept the communication request
How many times have I said it
A computer is a computer
Don't appear before me in my mother's likeness
I'm sorry, miss
The master requires that the communication feed in this room
must appear as Madam Ye's hologram
Now I'll block the video signal
Queen
What else do you want to say
If you won't help me leave here, forget it
So you want to stop me
Leaving the castle is strictly forbidden by your father
His orders take top priority
Hmph, top priority? Hahaha
If you still acknowledge yourself as the carrier of my mother's personality
then don't refuse me
I believe if Mother were still alive
she would agree with my actions
According to the data in my database
Madam Ye would not approve of your behavior
Then if the reason I run away from home is
to test whether Father still loves me?
After database analysis
Your father cares about you very much
Cares?
Caring means only providing food, clothing, and shelter
and not letting me contact the outside world?
Caring means making me every day
face only you bunch of
tin toys and electronic components?
This is what she calls caring?
I'd rather not have this kind of caring
Queen
Although I still cannot agree with you to this day
but your internal
Indeed, my mother's personality exists within me.
So I hope
you can help me fulfill this wish.
At the same time, I promise you
my plan will never give Father
a reason to blame you.
If this is what you think must be done,
then I support your decision.
But you only have five minutes of freedom at most.
Good luck.
Shaker,
let's begin the operation.
Got it.
Dottie... Dottie.
I will definitely—
Beautiful princess,
I've come to welcome you.
Cast aside your sorrow and greet the dawn with me!
Start running the virus program.
Where is Xiaoye?
Is she still in the room?
Master, I'm sorry,
Xiaoye is missing.
What exactly happened?
Early this morning,
I've been attacked by a computer virus.
The castle's security system went down for five minutes.
I think the culprit must have used that window to take Little Ye.
Do you think we should contact the police?
Hmph! Don't mention them to me.
If the police were any good at catching robbers,
my wife wouldn't have died in vain back then.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
Can you trace the source of the virus?
For safety reasons,
we must now reorganize all the data in the database.
Temporarily, we cannot investigate the virus source.
Your safety must also be guaranteed.
Quickly summon the best private detective in town.
I'll wait for them in the reception room.
Begin search.
Strange.
The symptoms of this virus are different from what Little Ye described.
The database is severely damaged.
The castle!!
Uncle, is this the client's home?
Yeah, Lord Ye is the wealthiest man in town.
Alright, alright, you two.
Can you please act normal?
We're gonna be late!
It's like a medieval palace!
So over the top.
Wonder if it'll be like in the movies—
A white-bearded butler greeting us!
Aah! A ghost!
Ghosts don't exist in this world.
You're so rude!
Showing up out of nowhere!
Don't you know scaring people can kill them?
Hawxing!
What are you doing here?
Someone invited me, of course.
Sorry!
Kept you all waiting.
Please follow the service bot to the meeting room.
Mr. Ye has been expecting you.
Wow! That's a huge computer!
What is this?
This is my wife's intelligent electronic replica.
An accident ten years ago...
...took my wife's life.
All these years...
I finally, with the power of technology...
...brought her back to life.
Hello everyone
I am the intelligent computer, Queen.
The suspect designated it for the exchange
Where is Miss Ye's Sea Princess statue?
The statue is stored in the castle
in the highest piano room
It can, through different melodies,
sense the player's emotions
and thus emit
lights of different colors
The Sea Princess statue
is the Ye family heirloom
Truly magical, huh
No wonder the criminal wants it
Lord Ye
Can you let me connect to the Queen's main database?
Let me analyze the data
and carry out the investigation
Please forgive me, I refuse
because my database contains
a large number of confidential Ye family documents
No, Hawxing
You can do that
The Queen and I will be present to supervise
Of course
But could you let them?
First, get out of this room.
Someone among them is way too loud.
What did you say?
Just admit you want to show off.
Why are you scolding me in such a roundabout way?!
Really noisy.
Night City Master
Can we go check out the princess's room?
Maybe there's a clue.
Locky
Come on, let's find clues together!
What's easy to find?
Absolutely nothing.
Uncle's so tricky.
Said they're going out to make a call.
Have the police provide covert backup.
Just leave us here wasting time.
Waste of time.
Of course.
What clues could there be?
If there's a clue
That rich man's robot already found it long ago.
Forget it.
Just take a casual look.
When Inspector Sima gets back, just say nothing new was found.
Huh? A rag doll?
Hey hey hey.
Jingjing.
Don't treat this place like your own home.
Or that poker face
will say we messed up the crime scene again.
Ouch.
Ow ow ow ow ow!
It hurts so much!
What's this?
[Email login: incorrect password]
Dang it! I should've learned more about computers.
Locky, what are you playing with?
[Logging in...]
Never thought they'd use music as the password.
High Tower Princess.
Is the gift to your liking?
Wishing you all the best with your escape plan. [P.S. Please destroy this letter before you leave. —Nintendough]
Awesome!
Now everything makes sense.
What makes sense?
Inspector Sima.
I found the best clue!
We've totally got this this time.
Just wait and see Hawxing embarrass himself, hahaha
Detective Chen
Please send it to the main computer room
A little accident happened here
Tomorrow, wave to me at the horizon
Every day is just sunrise and sunset
Turning into time, imagining more
Looking forward to every second and every moment in life
My bright eyes are sparkling
A smile facing the sunlight
Stepping quietly at the crossroads of Qian'an's home